JASON JEANETTE: Hi.
I'm Jason Jeanette.
DANIEL KLAPHEKE: This is another version of a counter to an arm bar defense.
Setting up the arm bar, I want to make sure I control one arm and with the same side and put that with same foot on his hip.
Remember to turn 90 degrees in bringing this leg up in a good situation.
I'll bring this one here and clamp this one straight down towards the floor, pinch the knees together and bridge up.
What we're going to soon know as he feels it coming or I'm just too slow.
If in this position he's going to stack me.
Okay?
He's going to stand me up on my neck which is not really comfortable.
I'm not ready to abandon my technique yet.
I'm going to maintain control of my left hand, just keeping it tight, keep my knees together and keep him from escaping.
I'm going to let go of my right hand, I'm going to grab his heel.
I'm going to lift this leg and throw it that way as I throw my feet towards the floor here, maintaining control, again keep my knees together and then bridge.